Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Box: 39, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Employees' Pensions, Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, 1950; Publication (Box 39, Folder 53)
- Box: 39, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Employees' Pensions, Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, 1952; Publication (Box 39, Folder 54)
- Box: 39, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 39, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Safety Digest, 1954; Publication (Box 39, Folder 55)
- Box: 39, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 39, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Your Job, Your Company and You, 1950; Publication (Box 39, Folder 56)
- Box: 39, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 39, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Traffic Department, 1954; Publication (Box 39, Folder 57)
- Box: 39, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 39, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Your Charm and Health, 1954; Publication (Box 39, Folder 58)
- Box: 39, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 39, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Employee Handbook, 1967; Publication (Box 39, Folder 59)
- Box: 39, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 39, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Management Development Program, 1961; Publication (Box 39, Folder 60)
- Box: 39, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 39, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Management Program Part I, 1950; Publication (Box 39, Folder 61)
- Box: 39, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 39, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Management Program Part II, 1950; Publication (Box 39, Folder 62)
- Box: 39, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 39, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: How To Conduct A Community Action Meeting, 1968; Publication (Box 39, Folder 63)
- Box: 39, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 39, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Training Materials, 1968; Publication (Box 39, Folder 64)
- Box: 39, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 39, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: A Handbook For Trainers, 1969; Publication (Box 39, Folder 65)
- Box: 39, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 39, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Employee Handbook, 1969; Publication (Box 39, Folder 66)
- Box: 39, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 39, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: The Tuition Aid Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 39, Folder 67)
- Box: 39, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 39, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Basic Medical Expense Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 39, Folder 68)
- Box: 39, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 39, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance With Double Indemnity For Accidental Death, 1963; Publication (Box 39, Folder 69)
- Box: 39, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 39, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: More Protection Against Serious Sickness and Injury, 1963; Publication (Box 39, Folder 70)
- Box: 39, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 39, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Employees' Pensions, Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, 1950; Publication (Box 39, Folder 71)
- Box: 39, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 39, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Performance Rating Manual, 1964; Publication (Box 39, Folder 72)
- Box: 39, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 39, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Machine Set-Up Operator, 1966; Publication (Box 39, Folder 73)
- Box: 39, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 39, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Handbook For Teacher Recruitment, 1964; Publication (Box 39, Folder 74)
- Box: 39, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 39, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Health Benefits For New Jersey Public & School Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 39, Folder 75)
- Box: 39, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 39, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Handbook For Public Retirement In New Jersey, 1964; Publication (Box 39, Folder 76)
- Box: 39, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 39, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 39, Folder 77)
- Box: 39, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 39, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Teaching Salary Guide, 1968; Publication (Box 39, Folder 78)
- Box: 39, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 39, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: A Plan For Life and Health Group Insurance For Salaried Employees, 1974; Publication (Box 39, Folder 79)
- Box: 39, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 39, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Management Department Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 39, Folder 80)
- Box: 40, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Instructor's Guide For Public Employee Training Courses, 1955; Publication (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Box: 40, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Conference Guide Sheets For Fundamentals of Supervision, 1956; Publication (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Box: 40, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Supervisor's Workbook In Fundamentals of Supervision, Publication (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Box: 40, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Discussion Outlines For Leadership In Supervision Department of Mental Hygiene, 1952; Publication (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Box: 40, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Duplication and Offset Printing, 1958; Publication (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Box: 40, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Duplication Offset Printing, 1959; Publication (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Box: 40, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Institute In Personnel Administration, 1954; Publication (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Box: 40, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Training, 1958; Publication (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Box: 40, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Telephone Operators Are Human, Publication (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Box: 40, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Instructor's Manual In Fundamentals of Supervision, Publication (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Box: 40, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Telephone Bulletin, Publication (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Box: 40, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Little Things", 1956; Publication (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Box: 40, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Supervisor's Workbook In Fundamentals of Supervision, Publication (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Box: 40, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Better Letter Writing Workbook, 1959; Publication (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Box: 40, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Advanced Techniques of Investigation, 1958; Publication (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Box: 40, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: T.V. Conference, 1958; Publication (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Box: 40, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Supervision In Action, 1961; Publication (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Box: 40, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1961, Publication (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Box: 40, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Institute On Methods and Procedures, 1959; Publication (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Box: 40, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Extracts From Management Development Program, 1964; Publication (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Box: 40, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1965, Publication (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Box: 40, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Work Simplification Program Summary Report, 1966; Publication (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Box: 40, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1965, Publication (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Box: 40, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Work Simplification Program, 1966; Publication (Box 40, Folder 24)
- Box: 40, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Public Administration Internship Program, 1960; Publication (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Box: 40, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Public Administration Interns and State Employee Trainees, 1960; Publication (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Box: 40, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Motor Vehicle License Examiners, Publication (Box 40, Folder 27)
- Box: 40, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Public Administration Interns and State Employee Trainees, 1959; Publication (Box 40, Folder 28)
- Box: 40, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Administration, 1959; Publication (Box 40, Folder 29)
- Box: 40, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Administration, 1958; Publication (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Box: 40, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1959, Publication (Box 40, Folder 31)
- Box: 40, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Telephone Bulletin, Publication (Box 40, Folder 32)
- Box: 40, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1957, Publication (Box 40, Folder 33)
- Box: 40, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Staff Conference Leadership, 1955; Publication (Box 40, Folder 34)
- Box: 40, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1953, Publication (Box 40, Folder 35)
- Box: 40, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1954, Publication (Box 40, Folder 36)
- Box: 40, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Office of Executive Director, 1959; Publication (Box 40, Folder 37)
- Box: 40, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Safety Through Forethought, 1955; Publication (Box 40, Folder 38)
- Box: 40, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Guide To The State Fire Training Program, 1954; Publication (Box 40, Folder 39)
- Box: 40, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Lesson Plans: Fire Training, 1951; Publication (Box 40, Folder 40)
- Box: 40, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: A Century of Songs 1852-1952, Publication (Box 40, Folder 41)
- Box: 40, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Comprehensive Health Insurance Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 40, Folder 42)
- Box: 40, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Outline of Proposed Program To Encourage Preparation For Retirement, 1956; Publication (Box 40, Folder 43)
- Box: 40, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Employee Benefits, 1953; Publication (Box 40, Folder 44)
- Box: 40, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: The 1956 Safety League, 1955; Publication (Box 40, Folder 45)
- Box: 40, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: The 1953 Accident Prevention Activity For Production Employees, Publication (Box 40, Folder 46)
- Box: 40, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Wage and Salary Administration, 1953; Publication (Box 40, Folder 47)
- Box: 40, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Training, Publication (Box 40, Folder 48)
- Box: 40, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Comprehensive Health Insurance Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 40, Folder 49)
- Box: 40, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Management Inventory and Development Program, Publication (Box 40, Folder 50)
- Box: 40, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: New York State and Local Government, 1958; Publication (Box 40, Folder 51)
- Box: 40, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Administrative Internship Program, 1961; Publication (Box 40, Folder 52)
- Box: 40, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Transmittal of Specification, 1969; Publication (Box 40, Folder 53)
- Box: 40, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Operating Procedures Performance Ratings For The 1951 Calendar Year, Publication (Box 40, Folder 54)
- Box: 40, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Specifications For Position In The New York State Civil Service, 1956; Publication (Box 40, Folder 55)
- Box: 40, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: 1956 Statistical Data On Public Employments In New York State, Publication (Box 40, Folder 56)
- Box: 40, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Work Performance Rating, 1959; Publication (Box 40, Folder 57)
- Box: 40, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Performance Rating Manual, 1965; Publication (Box 40, Folder 58)
- Box: 40, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Performance Rating and Appraisal Program, 1965; Publication (Box 40, Folder 59)
- Box: 40, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Performance Rating and Appraisal Program Manual of Procedures For State Agencies, 1965; Publication (Box 40, Folder 60)
- Box: 40, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Transmittal Memorandum No. 1, 1965; Publication (Box 40, Folder 61)
- Box: 40, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Report Of Work Progress Made By Public Administration Program Trainees 1950-1957, Publication (Box 40, Folder 62)
- Box: 40, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Classification and Compensation Plan and Salary Schedules, 1951; Publication (Box 40, Folder 63)
- Box: 40, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Transmittal of Specification, 1972; Publication (Box 40, Folder 64)
- Box: 40, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, 1956; Publication (Box 40, Folder 65)
- Box: 40, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Discussion Outlines For Leadership In Supervision Department of Mental Hygiene, Publication (Box 40, Folder 66)
- Box: 40, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 40, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Fundamentals of Supervision For Safety Supervisors, Publication (Box 40, Folder 67)
- Box: 40, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 40, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Discussion Outlines In Leadership and Human Relations For Department of Correction, Publication (Box 40, Folder 68)
- Box: 40, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 40, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Institute On New York State Government, Publication (Box 40, Folder 69)
- Box: 40, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Careers For College Graduates, 1952; Publication (Box 40, Folder 70)
- Box: 40, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 40, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Institute In Personnel Administration, Publication (Box 40, Folder 71)
- Box: 40, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Stationary Engineering Training Program Evaluation, 1951; Publication (Box 40, Folder 72)
- Box: 40, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 40, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Orientation To Division of Employment, 1960; Publication (Box 40, Folder 73)
- Box: 40, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, 1966; Publication (Box 40, Folder 74)
- Box: 40, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 40, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Careers For College Graduates In New York State Government, 1955; Publication (Box 40, Folder 75)
- Box: 40, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 40, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: A Guide To The Attendance Rules For Employees In New York State Departments and Institutes, Publication (Box 40, Folder 76)
- Box: 40, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 40, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Orientating New Employees, Publication (Box 40, Folder 77)
- Box: 40, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 40, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1955, Publication (Box 40, Folder 78)
- Box: 40, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 40, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Institute On Personnel Administration, 1959; Publication (Box 40, Folder 79)
- Box: 40, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 40, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Budgeting & State Finance, 1959; Publication (Box 40, Folder 80)
- Box: 40, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 40, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: First Interdepartmental Institute In Research and Statistics, 1959; Publication (Box 40, Folder 81)
- Box: 40, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 40, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Group Leadership Institute, 1959; Publication (Box 40, Folder 82)
- Box: 40, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 40, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Orientation Program, 1959; Publication (Box 40, Folder 83)
- Box: 40, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 40, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: New York State and Local Government, 1960; Publication (Box 40, Folder 84)
- Box: 40, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 40, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Administrative Adjudication In The Temporary State Housing Rent Commission, 1960; Publication (Box 40, Folder 85)
- Box: 40, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 40, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1960, Publication (Box 40, Folder 86)
- Box: 40, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 40, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: Orientation Program, 1960; Publication (Box 40, Folder 87)
- Box: 40, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 40, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Budgeting & State Finance, 1960; Publication (Box 40, Folder 88)
- Box: 40, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 40, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Budgeting & State Finance, 1960; Publication (Box 40, Folder 89)
- Box: 40, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 40, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Basic Electricity, 1964; Publication (Box 40, Folder 90)
- Box: 40, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 40, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Discussion Outline Fir Fundamentals of Supervision, 1964; Publication (Box 40, Folder 91)
- Box: 40, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 40, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Group Leadership Institute, 1959; Publication (Box 40, Folder 92)
- Box: 40, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 40, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Your Retirement Benefits, 1943; Publication (Box 40, Folder 93)
- Box: 40, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 40, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Conference Guide Sheets For Fundamentals of Supervision, 1955; Publication (Box 40, Folder 94)
- Box: 40, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 40, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: Personnel Services and Employee Relations, 1955; Publication (Box 40, Folder 95)
- Box: 40, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 40, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Survivor's Benefit Program, 1966; Publication (Box 40, Folder 96)
- Box: 41, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Performance Rating Manual, 1964; Publication (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Box: 41, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Courses In Employment Administration, 1920; Publication (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Box: 41, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Board Game, Publication (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Box: 41, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Tools, Wheels and Men, Publication (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Box: 41, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Group Hospital, Surgical and Medical Insurance Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Box: 41, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Funded Contributed Retirement Plan For Salaried Employees and Officers, 1946; Publication (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Box: 41, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: If You Work For A Railroad and., 1952; Publication (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Box: 41, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Here's The Easy Way For You To Invest In New York Central Stock, 1955; Publication (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Box: 41, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Group Hospital, Surgical and Medical Insurance Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Box: 41, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Supplementary Pension System, 1953; Publication (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Box: 41, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Safety Instructions, Publication (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Box: 41, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Safe Railroader, 1954; Publication (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Box: 41, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Safety Wherever, 1953; Publication (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Box: 41, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Company Manners, Publication (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Box: 41, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Service Committees Take A Hand, 1954; Publication (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Box: 41, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Telephone Pointers, 1954; Publication (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Box: 41, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: New York Central Calling, Publication (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Box: 41, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Special Apprentice Training Program, 1952; Publication (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Box: 41, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Improving Work Methods Part II, 1952; Publication (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Box: 41, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Improving Work Methods Part I, 1952; Publication (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Box: 41, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Training, 1955; Publication (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Box: 41, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Accounting Department Junior Management Training Program, Publication (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Box: 41, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Service Committees Follow Through, 1954; Publication (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Box: 41, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Conference's Leaders Guide, 1954; Publication (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Box: 41, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Proposed Merck Executive Development Program, 1952; Publication (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Box: 41, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Lateiner Method of Accident Control For Supervision, 1965; Publication (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Box: 41, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Manpower Development Training Program, 1967; Publication (Box 41, Folder 27)
- Box: 41, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Amendments, Publication (Box 41, Folder 28)
- Box: 41, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Training Programs 1967-1968, Publication (Box 41, Folder 29)
- Box: 41, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Training Program 1968-1969, Publication (Box 41, Folder 30)
- Box: 41, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Survey of The Employee Training Activities of New York City Agencies, 1958; Publication (Box 41, Folder 31)
- Box: 41, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Evening Courses For City Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 41, Folder 32)
- Box: 41, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Report of The Training and Career Development Division, 1961; Publication (Box 41, Folder 33)
- Box: 41, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Training Notes 1965, Publication (Box 41, Folder 34)
- Box: 41, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Inter-Agency Training Course, 1964; Publication (Box 41, Folder 35)
- Box: 41, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Cooperative Education Bulletin, 1965; Publication (Box 41, Folder 36)
- Box: 41, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Municipal Cooperative Education Trainees, 1965; Publication (Box 41, Folder 37)
- Box: 41, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Municipal Cooperative Education and Work Program, 1965; Publication (Box 41, Folder 38)
- Box: 41, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Report of The Evaluation Study of The Municipal Cooperative Education and Work Program, 1965; Publication (Box 41, Folder 39)
- Box: 41, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Interagency Training Course, 1968; Publication (Box 41, Folder 40)
- Box: 41, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Graduate Scholarships For City Employees, 1964; Publication (Box 41, Folder 41)
- Box: 41, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: The Career And Salary Plan and Standard Leave Regulations, 1959; Publication (Box 41, Folder 42)
- Box: 41, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Regulation Governing Performance Ratings, 1964; Publication (Box 41, Folder 43)
- Box: 41, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: The Career And Salary Plan and Standard Leave Regulations, 1960; Publication (Box 41, Folder 44)
- Box: 41, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Special Training Center, 1968; Publication (Box 41, Folder 45)
- Box: 41, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 41, Folder 46)